==> Project Setup <== 
1) I've used 'https://start.spring.io' to configure the Spring boot project
2) Added the dependency to allow the project to have Swagger:
		<dependency>
			<groupId>org.springdoc</groupId>
			<artifactId>springdoc-openapi-starter-webmvc-ui</artifactId>
			<version>2.6.0</version>
		</dependency>





==> Running the Program <==
To execute the program, follow these steps:
	1.	Open project with IDE and execute the application.
	2.	Open your browser and navigate to the following endpoint:
			http://localhost:8080/labseq?n=0
			http://localhost:8080/labseq?n=1
			http://localhost:8080/labseq?n=99..
Here, 'n' can be any non-negative integer (negative numbers are not allowed).

==> Swagger <==
Access the following endpoint:
http://localhost:8080/swagger-ui/index.html#/


==> Web GUI Implementation <==
I attempted to implement an optional JavaScript web GUI using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. You can access it via the IDE icon that opens in the browser at the following URL:
http://localhost:63343/labseq/labseq/src/main/resources/static/templates/index.html?_ijt=q245hc3e8ih6vg951h04bkaq49&_ij_reload=RELOAD_ON_SAVE

Note: The Screenshots folder contains an image named IDE.jpg, which shows the Rider IDE displaying the index.html file. In the top right corner, there are four icons (Rider, Chrome, Firefox, Safari). When selecting Chrome, it opens the URL above with port 63343.

Unfortunately, I encountered challenges with the aJax request from the frontend to the backend controller endpoint due to Cross-Origin Resource Sharing (CORS) issues. My goal was to send an aJax request to retrieve the labseq answer, but I couldn’t resolve the CORS problem. Because of this problem, i've opted to change the page location diretly using location.href whenever the button was pressed sending the 'n' that the user has written in the input.

Despite this problem, the experience was valuable, as I learned how to build a full-stack application with a properly structured frontend.



